contactout.com 2018-01-10

# Privacy Policy - ContactOut

Contactout Limited ("us", "we", or "our") operates the website https://contactout.com and the Contactout Chrome Extension (together, the “Service”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Information in connection with the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

Our Services aggregates personal information such as email addresses from publicly available sources on the internet. If you do not want your personal information to be included as part of our Service, you may opt out by contacting us at support@contactout.com

_Information gathered from visitors_

Log data: we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze Log Data. 

User data: we may ask for certain information such as an e-mail address when you register for an account. When you use the Contactout Chrome Extension to find email addresses we may collect the social media profile url, name, and social media profile information of the person you are requesting an email for. We use this information to match to our database and return an email address to you. 

Cookies: cookies are files with small amounts of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

_Marketing and promotions_

We may use your email to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you will be given the option to opt out or change your preferences.

_Sharing of your information_

We will not rent or sell the personal information of users of our Service. In future we may sell or divest the company. Your Personal Information such as customer names and email addresses and other user information related to the Service may be among the items sold or otherwise transferred in the event of a company sale.

_Security_

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information. However we can not warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and, where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information seems likely to have been compromised, and take other steps in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

_Visitor Options_

If at any time you wish to remove information collected by the Service about you, you may opt out by contacting us at support@contactout.com. You can stop receiving promotional email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided in such communications.

_How to contact us_

Please contact us at support@contactout.com if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy

_Changes to our privacy policy_

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 1 January 2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
